All right, let's get to this Richard
Hart stuff. Let's see what
>> Hello everybody. Richard Hart here. Hope
everyone's having a good Christmas. Some
of you aren't. Some of you Christmas
sucks. And so here I am to try and share
the Christmas spirit and the Christmas
joy with you. So we're here together. Uh
I hope wherever you are in the world
that you're making the best of it. Where
are we at? Well, we're at uh Bitcoin at
87.5.
>> Where are we at? Yo,
it's like yo, it's getting more and more
obvious that he's just watching me.
Um,
like when the [__] the last time you
heard somebody say where where we at
when it comes to crypto? Like,
>> uh, I hope wherever you are in the world
that you're the best of it.
>> That's what I say for all of my [__]
man.
>> Well, we're at uh, Bitcoin at 80.
>> Cuz your [__] when you watch people, you
they rub off on you.
I don't know if y'all noticed that, but
if you like watch somebody almost
religiously, it's kind of like being
around them all the time and your lingos
and stuff start to copy each other.
>> 7.5K word Ethereum.
>> Richard, just say you watching my [__]
man. I got some coming out anyway.
And yo, we got I don't want to make any
guarantees or anything, but less
it's coming out soon.
And um somebody else just hit me up
saying they want to partner and do you
know build something and just have it
compliment more too. So
we building over here man. I don't know
about everybody else
but uh allegedly some [__] is going on.
I mean I could be lying but I couldn't
be playing.
>> 2950
and all the RH founded stuff is wrecked.
Everybody's wrecked. Um, Prove X I think
did 16M of sack more or less 16.3M
and then the prices dumped for the sack
and then
>> yeah that whole plan like you surprised
by that. I guess that's what people are
doing. somebody uh bridged in or used
bridged in
I don't know bridged in something from
many months ago and then doubled the
price on Paulax more or less and then
the community sold it directly down
again right back down. So [laughter]
I don't know I thought uh I thought it
was a cool theory that uh the weekends
would be shaken out. Look new shiny
thing. Cool.
>> Duh.
>> And then the man the weekends are like
>> Yeah. Why would you I mean Yeah. Like
it's I It's kind of starting to get kind
of frustrating because it's like no we I
see through your [__] man. Like
[snorts] at first it was kind of hard to
see through it, but now it's like kind
of clear. It's like well duh. You made
it so they can't know about they have to
sacrifice postchain stuff. They have to
sell that stuff
to sacrifice. Where do you think they
gonna get the money from?
>> Who's the guy? The David Gogggins guy.
He just runs a lot. There's a pretty
funny image of David Gogggins
>> on the exhausted sellers
>> with the text is the sellers are
exhausted and underneath it says the
sellers. This picture of David Gogggins
running.
So yeah. Um a lot of everybody likes to
project what's so there's a recency
bias. So, anything that's recent is what
people assign causality.
>> I almost don't even feel like like this
is probably one of the first times I
don't even feel like really watching
this [__] How many views it got? 8,000.
I think it says last one got 18,000
>> too. So, like the news says, "Oh, price
is down. What just happened?" Okay, that
Well, that must be related. That's not
how real life works. Um,
>> it's kind of like, well, now we know you
don't know [__] You know what I'm
saying?
Well, I always knew that he was like a
regular person. Like the community is
who put him on like this godlike tier,
you know, thing. I always seen him as a
regular person. And you know, and his
calls were pretty spot on, but it's not
like he's going to know everything,
right? So sitting here trying to be
like, you know, well, actually things
are
>> does kind of wreck right now.
>> You you bought ETH at the top. I mean, I
was selling it.
You know what I'm saying?
You know, I did better than that. I
mean, I I wasn't dealing with the same
amounts, but
>> point is
>> I mean, not so many months ago, Ethereum
was $1,400 or $1,500. Now it's $3,000,
which sucks compared to the $5,000 it
was, you know, four years ago or a
couple even a few months ago. Look, four
years ago, it was up there. It was up
there to like 49
>> itself.
I don't know, maybe five months ago,
something like that. It's hard to
memorize all the charts across all
different time frames.
So, you know, when you're in a community
and you're looking at uh the prices and
you're wondering, well, what is it
that's going on in the community that's
affecting the prices, a lot of the times
it's things that are going on outside of
the community. So, you know, uh, crypto
has the most regulatory certainty, the
most, uh, adoption by legacy, the most
integration with banks, the best this,
the best that, the best SEC we've had in
years, you name it. And, uh, it's only
87.5K.
Four years ago, I called the top on the
day at 65K,
>> but come on, man. What you going to be?
What's next? 10 years ago, I called the
top on the day.
>> 20 years ago, back in my day, I called
the top on the day.
>> So, uh, you know, being up 20%. Not that
great when, uh, you know, gold's up
maybe 70% on the year, something like
that.
>> But look, China is buying gold to
replace their US dollar reserves.
China's not buying, at least to the best
of my knowledge, as much crypto as
they're buying gold. And that you see it
on the price chart, right?
You get it's
the cycle is interesting. So I said a
long time ago that Bitcoin was coming to
the top of its S- curve
and this is what the top of an S-curve
looks like. It looks like
>> Clint pumps. Um,
yeah, it's uh it's interesting. The
value the value proposition is still
there. Banks still suck as hard as they
ever have. Currencies still suck as hard
as they ever have. Who would really ever
make fun of Bitcoin for being 875,000
when I mined it for free when it was 50
cents? I mean, that's what nearly a
200,000x.
That ain't too bad.
Um,
but look if if everyone I called the
Rolex watch top on the day.
>> What is it?
>> Not on the day. Maybe like within
>> What else did I did? One time I jumped
my bike over the ramp and it went I went
three feet.
[laughter]
I remember one time
[__] he is definitely trailer pop
boys. Yo, is it Rick? Is his name Ricky?
a month of the top
>> and Rolex prices have been demolished.
AP prices are demolished. Um, crypto
prices are far lower than they were
months ago, right? This is not something
that's localized to whatever community
you're in. This is a global macro. You
know, things aren't
it's easy to predict the future when the
past and the current look real similar,
but things are weird, right? So,
government chose hyperinflation instead
of market dump and then the things that
hyperinflated are the things you didn't
have.
>> So, China started buying gold. uh people
bought the Magnificent 7 or the
Magnificent Five, whatever it is,
stocks, Nvidia, etc.
And then, you know, I think crypto has
kind of macro competition in that
there's so much gambling crap going on.
So, all this like sports betting I
believe competes with crypto and is
>> as simple as as simple as this, man. The
stable coins have to do better yield
than what they producing. Like the
stable coin yield needs to be way better
than a bank. It's stuff like that. The
the yield the return has to be better
than the other stuff. That's just all it
is, man. The return has to be better.
Like staking stable coins and, you know,
ETH and that stuff is cool, but the
return just from the yield isn't enough.
Like I'm at the point I'm like, damn, I
can just put this [__] in the bank, you
know, but just like the it's like the
risk of it being in there. It's like now
it can get taken from you. So it's like
it probably won't, you know, it's like
some super if you a a cipher punk, then
yeah, you might be kind of worried about
that. But I mean, it'll be happening to
regular people, too. But anyway, I
digress.
>> Thing for humans.
And then uh now that that
Sports betting has basically nothing in
common with crypto, but the people that
participate in it have similar mindsets.
They like excitement. They like things
that move fast.
You could call them low time frame
oriented. So, you know, when people want
to make 100x in a day,
it it's hard for them to zoom out. You
know, they they do whatever the new
shiny thing is or the thing is shoved
down their throat. And sports betting is
shoved down people's throat. And uh
prediction markets are similar to sports
betting.
So prediction markets, sports betting,
they're both not that great for crypto
in my opinion because they compete for
the same use cases. Well, they don't
they don't compete for the same use
cases, but they compete for similar
user experiences of yes, it could make
you rich or poor, right? It's like the
people that come in from It's crazy how
I skipped right there. It's like the
people that come in to crypto are the
same people that come in from gambling
basically. And those people aren't going
to filter out and go out and use a stuff
like that. They're not going down those
paths. They're going to the gambling
stuff and they're staying at the
gambling stuff. They're not getting any
yield. They're not trying to buy and um
invest. That's basically what's the
problem with memes and that why that
type of that type of stuff in crypto
actually is
bad for crypto. So it's
can you imagine if you were sitting at
Rolex headquarters and you're like man
why aren't Rolexes worth much anymore or
not as much as they were worth not so
long ago? I know a certain somebody that
lost a lot of millions of dollars on
their Rolex collection. Is it because of
prediction markets? Is it because of
sports betting?
>> Nah, not really. I mean, maybe a little
bit, but you know,
>> I like when he goes that direction.
That's the real Richard Hart right
there. The [__] that don't
really know [__] Like, you can see it
in his eyes. He's being a character. You
see the little boy come out of him right
here.
Is it because of sports betting?
>> Look how he looks at the camera.
>> Nah, not really. I mean, maybe a little
bit, but [laughter]
you know, so crypto being in the same
boat as
>> Rolex,
I don't know.
That [__] was adorable.
>> In the same boat as used car prices or
new like SF90 prices or whatever,
it's
people don't have money, right? Yeah.
>> So, you can come up with all the nice
narratives you want.
>> Yeah.
>> But the fact that watches and crypto and
lots of stocks that aren't
>> I once seen a a post that said, not a
post, but like something that somebody
said in like the 1920s. Oh, I forgot.
I'm I lost my train of thought. Never
mind.
>> 2007 or five.
>> Oh, a recession is when No. Yeah. A
recession is when people don't have
money. A depression is when you don't
have money. It's kind of like a play on
like even rich people. Even the rich
people are struggling.
>> There's just people.
>> That's how I know we're kind of like
some I mean, yeah, we're in some type of
depression. It's weird though. Like all
the stocks and stuff is up, but I think
that's because people aren't really in
stocks and stuff. The normal people
aren't.
>> That's what's up. It happens sometimes.
>> And then the stock market didn't really
go up that much unless you had a [__]
ton of stocks. So, it's like, yeah, so I
put a couple hundred percent probably. I
don't know, but it's not really a lot
>> times. And the guys at the Fed know
that, which is why they're starting to
lower rates. And traditionally, markets
crash after they lower rates. Will it do
it this time? I have no idea. I don't
know. This only happens once every very,
very long time, right? every 10 or 20
years you get one of these like the
rates went up now they're going back
down again things
and there's too many things I mean the
governments that are in control of these
things they're very hard to predict for
instance if you wanted to compete with
China and AI probably one of the worst
things you could do is make it so that
they couldn't buy Nvidia chips which you
control because it's a US company and
then you force them to go and make their
own stuff which they're very good at
making their own stuff. And so now
they're going to make their own stuff.
And the Chips Act, which made it illegal
to sell certain levels of strength of
chips to China, basically mid and long
term, forced China probably to become
dominant in that space. Not yet, but
what space aren't they dominant in?
Like not that many, right? I mean,
they're [__] aliens. Have you seen
them? Have you seen them? They're
aliens, man.
>> Well,
not gaming, not software,
not chip manufacturer yet, but any other
material thing. Solar.
>> It's funny cuz they probably look at us
the same way. Like we look like aliens.
Our big eyes. That's deep as hell, bro.
>> Batteries,
electric cars, drones. Speaking of
which, drones. The United States did
another very interesting law thing
today. The FCC said that it would not
allow the registration of new designs
from DJI,
the company that makes half of all the
drones in the world.
How does that benefit America? I don't
really understand. This would be like
stopping Americans from buying the best
chips or the best
I don't understand. I don't I don't
really understand how it improves the
national security situation to make sure
Americans have more expensive or less
selection less selection of drones. I
don't
I don't get it.
It's not like they're controlled by the
cloud and China could turn them on and
I don't know make them do evil. I I
don't understand. So now like
>> I really don't get it. I think the chips
act basically harmed United States
national security interests and I really
don't understand how
>> making it so that you can't buy a new
DHI drone helps.
>> Maybe someone can explain it to me. go
on X.com and post about it.
So, yeah, you're not specifically
wrecked price-wise
for reasons that are all too different
than Rolex and Ferraris and most other
stuff. So, the prices of things is based
on supply and demand. The amount of
money that people buy stuff, which
directly influences demand, has run
short. Maybe in part it's due to
tariffs. You know, people historically
don't understand what tariffs tend to
do. They tend to kind of feel like this.
You know, um the people get the same
stuff, but it costs them more money to
do it. People don't realize that tariffs
are paid by the consumer. It's just a
different kind of tax. They're not paid
by the manufacturer. They're not paid
they're paid by the importer. And when
the importer has to pay more, they're
going to charge you more. That's it.
Period. So yeah, long story short, I
liked crypto and watches and cars better
when the people were getting styi checks
directly into their mailbox and uh
buying the stuff that they liked. And
what they liked is exotic watches,
exotic cars, and crypto. So, you know,
crypto is this interesting thing where
it's a world-changing innovation that
really can improve the world and
increase man's agency
and self-reliance and removal of
middlemen, increasing of efficiency.
But to get there, to get all those nice
things, you have a lot of people FOMO
gambling and doing stupid stuff. It's
one of the few places where people doing
stupid stuff leads to positive outcomes
for humanity pretty much.
Um,
so what else is going on?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I don't know. I mean, I'm I'm
basically just here to tell you guys
that uh I'm here with you. I'm in the
same situation as you. I wish prices
were higher. I I I think [clears throat]
the there's a nonprofit foundation
United States
this sitting on nearly a million if not.
>> I think the sooner you know his
community realizes that he is just like
y'all,
that's when it starts to that's when it
can grow again. It can become another
movement
because he's still too high on this
pedestal. And um he's coming down
though. can see it like people are I'm
not I mean I'm not really seeing much on
the algorithm about post training stuff
anyway but I imagine that's because
less people are really talking about
that stuff.
So it's kind of it got to start back
from the grassroots already a million
LCDs LCD writing tablets that have a
market value of maybe this device were
similar would cost about $15 at Staples.
You can get them a lot cheaper on
Amazon, but not branded or maybe with
not, you know, without magnets, things
like that.
[sighs and gasps] You would wish that
you would just send stuff, branded merch
to people and uh they would just love
it. Like, yeah, this is awesome. They
jump right in. But if people don't have
money, it it doesn't matter what you
send them. Now, is everyone broke? No,
not everyone's broke. Uh if you had
bought the magnificent magnificent five
or seven, you probably got a lot of
money. Congratulations to you. Uh if
you've been holding gold forever or
silver forever, congratulations.
But this, you know,
>> Yeah, man. I wish I would have been
buying silver earlier, dog, cuz I was
looking at it. I was like, damn, in like
2020,
I was like, huh, I could just buy some
silver every, you know, week or
something like that. And I would do it,
but I wouldn't be consistent. And it
wasn't until like maybe a year or so ago
I seen that they had the auto the auto
buy um thing and I turned that on. That
was back when it's like maybe 20 or 30.
But um I mean it ain't but double like
it's like you have to have a [__] ton of
it.
>> Or uh it's cool. Like my sports cars,
those are
all the Jordans and LeBron's and all
that stuff that I bought the past couple
years is all up. They're all all I mean
might be one or two cars that ain't up,
but anything that's like a PSA 10 is up
higher. Michael Jordan, LeBron, Steph
Curry, it's up. Tom Lee's position.
Michael Sailor bought tons billions of
dollars of Bitcoin
and if he were to try and sell right
now, he'd probably be cash negative
after the price slipped against him. And
Tom Lee bought tons billions of dollars
of Ethereum. And if you were to sell
right now, the slippage would also
probably put him cash negative.
You might be cash negative without
having had to buy billions of dollars.
[laughter]
It's like, man, where do these guys get
the coins to sell? My goodness.
Like if you if you look [clears throat]
at Pulseex, so Paulex now has burnt what
people consider to be 8.5% of the like
what they call the retail supply. I'm
not sure how accurate the term is, but
uh that's a lot of coin burning.
It makes you wonder. I I've tried to
explain hearts lot. Crypto needs another
thing like had the meme coins, it had
the NFTts.
The prediction markets isn't really
coins, [snorts] you know. So,
and it is, but it's not.
So yeah, it needs another thing
>> a
>> lot of people and there's there's a
specific nuance to it in that
if you have a coin that is tied to
stable coin and a pair when someone
wants to buy your coin, the bot has to
buy the other side of the pair. So, so
if you want if you bought Trumpcoin and
it was tied with USDC
and it was on the Salana network, you
had to turn your Salana into USDC to get
the Trump out and then the trading pair
has more USDC. And the net effect is
that the Salana got sold for USDC in
order for someone to get Trump. So, it
was a net down on the system. And so
when you look at blockchains and their
prices,
>> if you have something,
>> I was always wondering like why did they
put USDC? Like I kind of knew why
because well my reasoning was if they
paired it with USDC it's independent of
what Salana does. So if Salana goes down
it's not going to go down. I mean it
might but it's not going to be pulled in
any direction by Salana. But that is
true. They would have to set it might
have been a SCOP to crash the [__]
appreciates on a chain but its majority
is tied to tied to stablecoin.
[clears throat] Other people will sell
the native token.
>> You mean like provex?
Caught your ass. Exactly.
So you're saying prove X is a way to
send it down,
>> get the stable to get the uh the coin
that they want. Like
>> so you have this I don't know if you
call a dilemma but like a design space
decision where [clears throat] if things
run and they're tied to stable you might
nuke the other coins compared to stable.
And so if you like reflexivity you want
everything tied.
>> Really imagine you sacrificed for
provex. You sold your pulse and pulse x
and stuff to sacrificing the provex.
Peruvax comes down and [__] dumps,
bro. And then Post Shane and all that
[__] is send him from the bottom. That's
probably was I mean, but then still like
giving them too much credit. Like that's
what I would do, but maybe he's not as
smart as me.
>> Everything else,
>> but if something nukes, it hurts
everything else.
>> If we look back at what the history of
what everything did like, yeah, he used
hex and stuff for the first one to pump
the price of them. You know what I'm
saying? And now it's like, well, [__] I
gotta get it down lower so I can buy
more of the supply off the bottom,
you know? So,
yeah,
>> runs, it helps everything else as long
as everything's priced in the native.
And so you wonder, you're like,
you almost want to do the science and do
the math and look at like what would it
look like if everything on the chain was
majority tied to stable and then when
something ran.
I mean, my gut feeling is that the
reflexivity is still the way to go
because you've seen it work so many
times. You know, you you saw Salana go
up when everyone was in the trenches
launching new tokens. Yeah. Um,
you saw Ethereum go up when people were
launching ICOs on it.
>> I stable coins don't help, man. The kind
of thing that was worrying me cuz every
like stable coin, oh, stable coins is
going to be I'm like, yo, stable coins,
they don't do [__]
>> It's not making me do anything. It's not
It's not actually not bullish for I
could see how it could get more people
onto the chain, but as far as like
making the prices go up, no, that's not
I don't see how that's going to do
anything to the price. And that was
concerning.
>> The reflexivity of everything tied to
native is probably the right play
because I've never seen it work any
other way. I've never seen a chain where
the majority of the coins were tied to
stables and then
in like
Yeah, I don't know. It would be one of
those interesting thought experiments.
There's there's other like interesting
thought experiments. Like
>> just a reminder that um I'm going to be
well I plan to be doing more streams
um [snorts] talking about less once the
new year hits. Once we're out of this um
Christmas break, I'm going to be back on
it live
making content
um and we're going to be
speculating on less and more
nested liquidity layers. So, what if
coin A is tied to coin B and then B is
tied to C and then C is tied to D and
then A moves up. Well, how much
reflexivity is there between BC, CC, and
D on a on a graph, on a chart? I think
it'd be real fun to see that kind of
chart.
[sighs] Yeah. So, battle plan,
[clears throat]
people still buy garbage, lots of it,
billions of dollars of it. I think that
they would buy something better if it
were offered to them. And unless you've
refined and done every single thing that
you can think of to have an effective
sales pitch, an effective user
experience, a unique value proposition,
you should work to that end. So right
now, the Pulsechain ecosystem I feel is
really good. The software is reliable.
The software has been up years. The
front ends have stayed up and been more
durable against supply chain attacks and
everything else that they were designed
better than other people's. You don't
have uh like for instance the A
ecosystem is getting wrecked by
infighting between A Labs which uh
builds some software and the DAO being
starved of buy and burn. So they're
they're being starved of trading fees.
The Dow's upset about it. So that price
is nuking due to internal political
pressure. Paul Sax is sweeter. It's like
you know the buy and burn works great.
It doesn't have this stupid arguing
stuff.
Everything is just designed really well,
works really well. But in a world where
Rolex can't hold their price up, and uh
all of crypto can't hold its price up,
hey, guess what? Your price is going to
be down. And so, what's the trick?
What's the magic trick? The magic and
the trick is to keep building things
that help each other over and over and
over again.
And I feel that eventually you get to a
bottom where the number of people on
ramping and the economic energy in
exceeds the economic energy out.
>> [__] got to get built, man. And I'm just
that's why I'm saying like I'm not it's
kind of worrying me like this is one of
the first times
that I can remember that I've been in
crypto and I can't I'm not actually the
only thing I'm looking towards is my own
[__] My own crypto. That's the only
thing I see coming out.
there's and just prove that [__] But I
mean that's that's just a a a scop to
get the prices to go down. So I'm not
even sacrificed for that [__] Um
and if I'm wrong or wrong, I don't I
don't care. Um but yeah, there's nothing
else coming out. So,
you know,
I got this. I mean, I don't know. It's
just I can't help but think maybe like,
yo, what if this is the time that ain't
nothing coming out and my [__] just take
off, bro? It's so addicting. It's so
perfect. Oh my god. It could I don't
know, man. That'd be crazy though.
>> I don't think people have
>> And it could go really bad. It could go
really bad and maybe it comes out and
it's [__] you know,
it's it it gets hacked or something or
breaks. That would suck. infinite coins
they can sell and and I think people
if they are exposed to multiple options
and are able to evaluate some of those
options being better than others they
should buy the better thing. I think
that the Pulse chain, Pulse X, Hex,
>> how is it better?
>> Soon to be ProveX stuff.
>> Let's hear it.
>> I think it's just better.
>> How?
>> I think there a lot of stuff out there
is trash. But people buy the trash
because it's what's offered to them. So,
whatever it takes, whether it's email or
phone calls or going door todoor or
figuring out better texts to include
with your free merchandise, say an LCD
writing tablet, whatever those things
are is what you have to do because
people are getting pitched trash
constantly here. Sports betting here,
prediction markets here, bet whether a
guy says this word or that word. That's
not going to move society forward. That
that doesn't build lasting value.
the things in this ecosystem that keep
reinforcing each other. I mean, that
8.5%
that people talk about being burnt on
pulse, I think that eventually has an
effect. Those coins are gone forever.
They're burnt. There's no inflation.
They can only burn.
>> Hey, you want to see something too? Is
this right here?
>> Look at the LP for more. Look at this on
on the sell side. Look at the the ratio.
$5,000 worth of more. That's all that's
left. It's like all been burnt
with 26,000 buy side.
It's kind of like what he's talking
about with once, you know. I don't know,
man. But it seems like yeah, if you burn
all the coins and then the demand, you
know, starts to stay the same or floor
out,
it's going to offset and send the other
direction. Build more things like that,
eventually the supply just keeps
shrinking and then whenever you drip in
some demand, it should hit harder. So
that's that's a theory and that's what I
believe in. And look, I've been here
through not so many months ago, Ethereum
was 1,500 bucks. Months, homies. Not
years, months,
>> homies.
>> Not. And before that, Ethereum went from
1500 to 88.
Two digits. 88. That was four or five
years ago, right? 20 maybe late 2021, I
think.
>> What?
He say Bitcoin or Ethereum.
He must have been talking about Bitcoin.
Yeah. Say what? He didn't get no 8,000.
>> So this stuff's volatile and Rolex is in
the same boat you're in and sports cars
are in the same boat you're in. The
magic is to just keep doing what you
know works or what you believe will
work. And
>> I think that having inbound and outbound
>> sticking with my guns,
I know how to build. I mean, I don't
know how to code, but I know how to
build on top of stuff and keep that
engine going.
>> Would be great. I think that having look
if if if spokespeople need tried, if hot
AI chicks with big boobs need tried,
whatever whatever is working for the
rest of the world. If you look, if you
consume adult content, which I came up
with a funny phrase for, which I I
haven't told anybody yet, but it was
something along the lines of porn is
where you pay people to not have sex
with you. Or no, porn is where you pay
people to have sex, but not with you.
Something along those lines. I'm sure I
could massage it into a good a good
tagline or saying,
but some of those people in those porn
videos, not that I would ever watch such
a thing, but some of those people in
porn videos are watching crypto gambling
uh logos, URLs on their clothes, so you
can't like remove the watermark. Yeah.
>> Porn post sex porn campaign. You're
giving people ideas again. Someone could
put shirts on porn stars from it. Could
be done.
>> Not for years. It must work a little
bit. Maybe that's something somebody
should try.
>> See,
>> you got to try all the things, right?
>> You're too predictable, man.
>> Until you have literally tried all the
things.
>> Yeah, go ahead.
>> The game is you try every single thing.
You see what works and you stick around
long enough so that when people have
money again, they rotate into the better
thing instead of the worst thing. I mean
it kind of I mean the branding
pulsechain pulse
pulsechain.com
[laughter]
>> that might get actually might do really
well in porn because it's postchain like
chains
and I think it'll work and while
everyone else disappears they all go
away I persist. I don't go away. I stay
here and not because I need to be here
but because I need to be here. It's a
mental thing.
>> [laughter]
>> I know. I am here for glory. I want my
glory. And I think we have the tools
that we need to get it. And the stuff
that we have now is far better than it
ever was before. I mean, hex ate $50
million of cell pressure just to pay gas
fees on the Ethereum network.
That sucked. Doesn't have to do that
again.
Uh on everything is reinforcing
everything else. I think it's really
really cool. I believe in it and I'm
just going to keep talking about what I
believe in. So, I believe in this stuff.
I hope you guys are having a good uh a
good Christmas, as good as it can be.
And you got to put things into
perspective.
There's some people that have all the
money in the world, none of the freedom.
>> Yeah.
>> Money they can't spend.
>> There's some people that have all the
freedom and no money. And then there's
those people that are
>> It's kind of crazy, man. Like a thing
I've been going through the past couple
of years, man. This boredom is getting
[__] going insane, bro. I'm bored out
of my mind. I'm like trying to explore
hobbies and stuff and get that freedom
back. It's kind of weird how it's
happening.
>> Enough to appreciate what they have. And
those are the rich people. The rich
people are the people that appreciate
>> because you can't I mean, you can when
you're older, but at my age, you can't
just sit around, man. Like, it doesn't
feel right. And it doesn't really It's
like wasteful. You got to do something.
they have and there's always something
you could appreciate.
Try as
>> so if you're like in your 20s and 30s
and you're like I'm trying to I'm trying
to grind so I ain't got to work no more.
It's like it's not going to it's not it
doesn't work like that. No matter how
hard you grind and you got all this
money you just all I'mma stop here. No,
you can't. You're going to get bored.
>> I might I'm not one of those uh happy
types. You should be one of them. you're
going to be more effective, joyously,
happy about the the process, you know,
the uh the journey, so to speak.
Um,
if you can do that, more power to you.
It's free. It's It's free to appreciate
what you've got and it's the only thing
that'll make you truly feel wealthy.
There's a lot of people that have a lot
worse than you. If you're watching this,
you got internet, congratulations. You
got a screen, congratulations.
You've got speakers, you've got hearing
frags, bro.
>> I mean, congratulations. You got a lot
of things going for you. You should
focus on them in Christmas because
otherwise you'll be like me,
>> not that happy, but working very, very
hard.
It no amount of not money could change
what I want. What I want is glory. And
my glory is not going to come from uh
from just money. It's going to it's
going to come from the success of the
things I built. And I tell you another
thing that people don't understand. You
know, a lot of silent guys, they click
sell. Who do you think it hurts when
they click sell? Well, it hurts the
price chart for people that are looking
at it, but they're selling into like uh
my personality. [laughter]
My life sucks worse when other people
press sell.
That sucks, man. You know, a lot of you
guys out there, when people press sell,
it doesn't directly affect your image of
yourself. It's probably not that healthy
to uh associate your feeling of success
in life, no matter how hard you work,
with things outside your control, like
the prices when everything's
>> Damn, I never even thought about that.
Ethereum, that's some real [__]
Richard.
>> Damn. So, you I I mean, I I get it. You
attribute your your value to the the
chart. So, if you see it going down, it
makes you it makes you sad and it makes
you feel like you're not good enough.
That's that's crazy, man. That's that's
some good [__] to let out. I'm glad you
let that up.
>> Should be down
cheaper by nearly half after four years.
Why did they not work hard enough? You
know what I mean? Did uh do you think
Bitcoin after Sailor bought who knows
how many billions of it should be
sitting at a a limp dick 1.2x over 65K
from four years ago? That sucks, right?
But you do you build look Amazon dropped
95% too.
It happens right the markets are
fickle fickle beings and if you want to
win you keep doing what works. Oh people
want to sell cool sell please
go away great. Whether people buy or
sell or not doesn't affect whether you
built the right ecosystem, the right
machinery, the the right marketing
tactics, the right narratives. Doing
those things and building those things
is completely unrelated to whether
people recently bought or sold or not.
The focus is on whether you should feel
proud in the things that you've built
and the things that you're doing. The
price is going to go up and down
regardless. Ethereum is the same thing
it was when it was $1,500 not so long
ago and then $5,000 and now 2850 or
2950. It's the same stuff more or less
and the prices move around a lot and
that's life and you just want to
keep doing the things that you can be
proud of. And some people they just
disappear and that's all right too. you
know, not everybody's cut out to uh
to suffer the slings and arrows of
outrageous fortune. Anyway,
>> yeah, it's facts, man. Cuz you think
about people like Jake Shark,
he just disappeared.
Titan X is actually looking pretty
decent, though, as far as like
the ROI.
Like I said, it's said 124% now for a
max stake. So
regardless of him of Jake Sharp coming
back, I mean, he's got to turn the
buying burn on. All right. So, I mean,
that's the only that's the one thing.
But other than that, see, I solved all
of this, like all this
founders waiting on, you know, waiting
on founders to hit buttons and stuff.
Same thing with Rich Hart. You're
waiting on him to hit the button, you
know. Um, I want to build something that
you don't have to wait on me to hit a
button.
So,
um,
but this is I mean
after this payout, that's going to be it
for Titan X, but I think it might run
going into this because it's really
profitable to stake right now. So,
there's that.
But, um,
yeah, most founders, they can't handle
that heat of the the chart. And I think
that's what's happening. Like they run
away from it, disown it.
You see on my screen, I still got more
all over the screen.
You know what it is over here.
>> Merry Christmas everybody. Uh there's a
lot of people out there.
>> And buy more.
Look at this ratio, man. I mean, not
financial advice, but
it's fun.
Uh,
talk to y'all in the next one.
You know what? I feel like I'mma upload
this video publicly. Um,
so let's give you I'm going to give you
guys a taste of what a member video is
about. It's basically about the stuff
that I'm I'm looking at currently. It's
like I don't even want to show you. I
don't even want to show you, but
everything I'm paying attention to is
like a clock, you know? I'm trying to
not pay attention to stuff that
has some founder that can do something
or they we're waiting on them to build
something.
Um, what's else? Oh, Bitcoin's dumping.
It was looking good. Wow. It just the
the beginning of the video it was up
here. It's like 88 something, right?
Yeah, it's having some trouble, man.
Um, if we look at the stock to flow,
you know,
I've always said, you know, this is the
chart that
you want to follow.
And um, until it doesn't work, and so
far it's doing exactly like it's
supposed to, topping out around 900 days
from the having
and then starting to turn green as we go
down. So,
I'm fairly bearish, man.
Hopefully, I'm wrong. Hopefully, this is
invalidated and we pump and it's turning
green up here. Hopefully, I mean, but
not really, though. [laughter] Because
if that happens, that means this doesn't
work anymore. And I got to figure out
some other, you know, model. But this is
the one right here. You can see that
whenever we get 900 days or so from the
having, we're topping out. And whenever
we get around, you know, 400, 300, 400
days from the heaven,
that's when it starts to bottom.
So, here we go again. We got another
what year or so, but this is about 900.
We're about 900 days,
maybe about 800. It's kind of green a
little bit.
So, we're about not that far. About a
year, about a year out from it being
green. And it's not bad, man. Oops.
So,
yeah,
it's it's unfortunate, but it has to
happen. So, ultimately, what I think
we're going to I hope I'm wrong, you
know, hopefully we at least get a rally
up to like 95 or something again, but I
think over the long term, I think we're
going to go down and meet the uh mining
cost of Bitcoin. Right now it's at like
71.
Um, [snorts]
so by the time we get there maybe it's
at like 73 or something like that. But I
think we just
and then we get ready for that next.
Um,
hopefully I'm wrong though.
Uh,
let's check out more. Literally starting
from the bottom,
19 total stakers. That's insane
with 25 stakes. [snorts]
Um,
yeah, more tokens.com.
Where my [__] at?
Hold up. I'm rusty, y'all.
Where my button at?
Oh, it's right here.
>> I love it.
>> There we go.
Um,
I like seeing it small like this because
it just tells me that we're we're we can
grow from here. I mean, I don't even
talk about it.
Um, that's about it though, man. Become
a member.
And uh look out for less. Talk to you on
the next one. Peace.